Our goal in the remaining videos is to start
在接下来的几个视频中
looking into some of the details of what SageMaker is doing.
我们将开始学习 SageMaker 的详细运行过程
To do this we will start by looking at the Boston Housing example that we started with,
我们将首先看看一开始的 Boston Housing 示例
except instead of using the high-level API,
但是我们将使用低阶 API
we're going to use the low-level one.
而不使用高阶 API
This way we can see all of the steps that need to be taken,
这样可以了解需要完成的所有步骤
and all of the objects that are created along the way.
以及在此过程中创建的所有对象
If you'd like to follow along,
如果你要跟着操作
navigate into the tutorials folder and open up
请转到 Tutorials 文件夹
the Boston Housing-XGBoost Batch Transform Low-Level notebook.
并打开 Boston Housing-XGBoost (Batch Transform) Low Level notebook
I've already opened up the notebook here,
我已经在这里打开了该 notebook
and I've run the first few cells.
并且运行了前几个单元格
In beginning of this notebook is the same as the high-level version that you did earlier.
此 notebook 的开头与之前的高阶版本一样
A quick word of explanation before we get started.
在开始之前 先简单解释下
The reason for looking closely at the details is so that when
了解运行细节的原因是
errors inevitably show up they're easier to diagnose.
不可避免地出现错误时 更容易诊断错误
SageMaker's high-level API make some choices on your behalf,
SageMaker 的高阶 API 代表你做出了一些选择
which can be great when you want to get something done,
当你想完成任务时 这样很方便
but can be a little more problematic when things go wrong.
但是如果出现问题 则比较麻烦
So, now that we've downloaded the data and done some initial processing,
我们下载并初始处理了数据
it's time to upload the data files to S3.
下面将数据文件上传到 S3
As before the way we do that is to first save
和之前一样 首先将文件
the files locally inside of the notebook instance.
保存到本地 notebook 实例中
To do that we start by making sure that a directory exists inside of the data subfolder,
我们需要确保 /data 子文件夹中有相应目录
and then we use Pandas to save those files to the directory we've chosen.
然后使用 Pandas 将这些文件保存到所选的目录下
To see where those files have been saved,
为了查看这些文件的保存位置
if we select the tab that shows the notebook hub,
选择 Notebook Hub 所在的标签页
and we navigate up one directory,
然后返回上一个目录
we can see that there's a folder called data,
可以看到里面有一个文件夹 叫做 data
inside of the Data folder is another folder called Boston.
在 data 文件夹里有另一个文件夹 叫做 boston
Now, if you remember from the notebook.
我们在 notebook 中
We're saving the Data to the Boston subdirectory of the data directory.
将数据保存到了 data 目录的 boston 子目录下
Heading back to the notebook hub page,
回到 Notebook Hub 页面
inside of the Boston subdirectory we can see the test,
在 boston 子目录下可以看到
training, and validation csv files that we created using Pandas.
使用 Pandas 创建的测试 训练和验证 csv 文件
Now that the files have been saved on the notebook instance,
文件保存到 notebook 实例中后
we can upload them to S3.
我们将文件上传到 S3
Remember to do that,
我们将使用
we use the upload data method of the session object.
session 对象的 upload_data 方法上传文件
Before we do this,
在此之前
let's talk a little bit about what S3 is.
先讨论下什么是 S3
In essence, S3 is Amazon's data storage facility.
S3 本质上是 Amazon 的数据存储工具
It provides a place for you to store data that you might want to read many times.
它为你提供了一个数据存储位置 你可能希望多次读取这些数据
For example, training data or a saved model.
例如 训练数据或保存的模型
If we open up the AWS console page,
我们可以打开 AWS 控制台页面
which we can do by clicking on the AWS icon in the top left corner,
方法是点击左上角的 AWS 图标
and scroll down and look under storage for S3.
向下滚动并在 storage 下找到 S3
We can open up the S3 console.
打开 S3 控制台
This will show you any buckets,
这里会显示所有的存储桶
remember a bucket works like a drive that you have created inside of S3.
存储桶就像在 S3 里创建的驱动器一样
Currently, I don't have any buckets.
目前我没有任何存储桶
If I go back to the notebook and I execute this cell,
如果我回到 notebook 中并执行此单元格
SageMaker tells me that the default bucket
SageMaker 将告诉我
associated with this notebook instance has been created.
与此 notebook 实例相关的默认存储桶已经创建
Now if I navigate back to the S3 console and refresh the page,
现在回到 S3 控制台并刷新页面
I can see the S3 bucket that has been created.
可以看到已经创建了这个 S3 存储桶
Further, if I select this and open it up,
选择并打开此存储桶
we can see that there's a single directory,
可以看到里面有一个目录
again with the same name that we specified in our notebook,
名称与在 notebook 中指定的名称一样
and inside of that directory are the test train and validation files.
在该目录下有测试 训练和验证文件